Wa! You guys, this mini show is going to
be incredible. I'm so excited. Okay,
let's go to the checklist. Mirrors,
>> check.
>> Directions.
>> Directions in Desert Valley, check.
>> Next,
>> check.
>> Seat belts,
>> check. Check.
>> New driver's license,
>> check.
>> You guys are ready to go? You got the
directions on your phone, right?
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. They can't use
your phone while driving. It's
dangerous.
I'm sure they'll be responsible. Isn't
that right?
>> Iceber is responsible.
>> There you go.
>> All right. You are the captain of the
van now. Take care of your crew and they
will take care of you.
>> Iceber understands.
>> Road trip. ROAD TRIP. Road trip.
Road trip.
>> Have fun.
>> Slow down.
[music]
>> Sunny day.
Think only for the morning.
something out for you. Cuz all of a
sweaty weather is no bother.
Let's fly away.
[music] Let's fly away. So far away.
So far away.
>> Uh-oh. Guys, we have a problem. We're
already out of Star Cakes. We got to
stop to refuel.
>> And I got to use the little panda's
room, please.
>> Oh, let's stop there.
They'll have snacks and bathroom stuff
and dinosaurs.
>> Iceber does not want to make stops
unless emergency
please. Come on. Come on.
It's the one thing he's not good at.
>> Huh? Go get cakes. Iceber will wait in
car.
>> All right, ma'am. If you say so.
>> I'll be back in the drift.
Oh, sweet relief. I think I can make it
a whole two hours now. Where's older
brother?
>> I found you.
This is a pretty car. My mom had one,
but she pushed it down a ravine.
[laughter]
>> Wyatt. Oh, good. You found the car. Hey
guys, I want you to meet Wyatt. He got
separated from his motorcycle gang and
needs a ride.
H.
It's true. I I wouldn't lie to y'all.
I'm in a legit motorcycle gang. I told
him he could hitch a ride with us.
That's cool, right? Hey, I guess we can
make room for one more.
>> Yeah, alert.
>> Wyatt not part of plan. Wyatt not
coming.
>> Oh, okay. It's just I got all these
snacks and now I got no one to share
them with.
>> Okay, I call the vote. All the Wyatt and
the Star Cakes aboard. Say I. I.
>> I.
>> I. Welcome to the crew, Wyatt.
>> Everyone was pretty happy and stuff.
Then I said, "If y'all come back, I'll
feed you to my tarantula." And that's
how I got rid of those kitty cats.
>> I mean, it sounds like, please, please.
>> Huh?
>> Oh, no. The phone's on low battery.
>> You didn't bring the charger?
>> I forgot it.
>> Without directions, we'll get lost in
the desert forever.
>> Iceber will pull over and buy map.
>> Don't worry, gang. I keep a spare
charger in my boot. Wyatt, you saved us.
>> You're the best, Wyatt.
>> Wyatt, you're so prepared for trips.
Maybe you should be captain.
>> Oh, stop it. It's nothing at all,
really.
>> I say this calls for a special
celebration. Who wants to watch you eat
like six of these cakes at once?
>> Oh, it grizz.
>> Remember, use napkin.
>> Don't worry, I'll be careful.
>> No, use napkins.